// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the name of the young girl on this story?",
    answer: "Buhle",
    options: [
      "Marcia",
      "Pretty",
      "Thando",
      "Buhle"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the name of the sport that Buhle loved?",
    answer: "Net-ball",
    options: [
      "Soccer",
      "Net-ball",
      "Cricket",
      "Tennis"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "When would Buhle go to the nearby Net-ball court?",
    answer: "Every practice and at every game",
    options: [
      "Every Monday",
      "Every Sunday",
      "Every practice and at every game",
      "Everyday"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What did the coach notice about Buhle?",
    answer: "She loved the sport and knew the rules like a referee",
    options: [
      "She did not want anything to do with the sport",
      "She hated the sport",
      "She enjoyed watching the sport",
      "She loved the sport and knew the rules like a referee"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What did the coach ask from Buhle?",
    answer: "She asked her to come be their referee",
    options: [
      "She told her to go home",
      "She asked her to come be their referee",
      "She asked why does Buhle keep coming to the court",
      "She asked nothing"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What did the coach give Buhle?",
    answer: "She gave her a referee kit and a whistle",
    options: [
      "She gave her a card",
      "She gave her a ball",
      "She gave her a referee kit and a whistle",
      "She gave her nothing"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What did Buhle forget at home?",
    answer: "The whistle",
    options: [
      "She forgot to come to the game",
      "The referee kit",
      "The whistle",
      "She forgot her hat"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "How was Buhle at judging the game?",
    answer: "Really great at it",
    options: [
      "Too bad",
      "Really great at it",
      "She did not know what she was doing",
      "She massed up the game"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "How did the coach feel about Buhle after the game?",
    answer: "She was very pleased",
    options: [
      "She was disapointed",
      "She was angry at Buhle",
      "She regreted giving Buhle a chance",
      "She was very pleased"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What lesson did Buhle learn that day?",
    answer: "Make sure you have everything you will need everytime you are going to do something",
    options: [
      "She did not learn anything",
      "Make sure you have everything you will need everytime you are going to do something",
      "Do not care you have everything you will need everytime you are going to do something",
      "Make sure you have nothing on you everytime you are going to do something"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];
